{
    "id": "4d40ba60019d4c91876240b18e9bcfd4",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was in such a …………………………. She didn’t know to whom to turn.",
            "description": "When you are in a quandary, you are in a dilemma.",
            "answers": [
                "quandary",
                "quadrary",
                "quarantine"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The dictator’s army …………………………. the rebellion.",
            "description": "All of these words can mean suppress or crush.",
            "answers": [
                "quashed",
                "squashed",
                "quelled",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The door was …………………………… left open.",
            "description": "Purposely means deliberately.",
            "answers": [
                "purposely",
                "purposefully",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The student ……………………………. studied all night in order to secure good grades.",
            "description": "When you do something purposefully, you do it with a specific goal in mind.",
            "answers": [
                "purposely",
                "purposefully",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If he drank too much he would become ……………………………..",
            "description": "Pugnacious means quarrelsome.",
            "answers": [
                "pungent",
                "pugacious",
                "pugnacious"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His …………………………….. remarks started an argument.",
            "description": "The correct expression is provocative. ",
            "answers": [
                "provocational",
                "provocative",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… laws discouraged the drug trade.",
            "description": "Both words mean the same prohibitive means restrictive.",
            "answers": [
                "Prohibitive",
                "Prohibitory",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The family’s …………………………… was pitiable.",
            "description": "Privation means poverty.",
            "answers": [
                "privation",
                "privilege",
                "privacy"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He had nothing left of his inheritance because of his ………………………………… ways.",
            "description": "All of these words mean wasteful.",
            "answers": [
                "prodigal",
                "spendthrift",
                "wanton",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "It took a great deal of …………………………. to insult the mayor at his own party.",
            "description": "All of these words mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "presumption",
                "audacity",
                "impertinence",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "His mother’s work as a nurse ……………………………… him to become a doctor.",
            "description": "To predispose is to encourage or urge.",
            "answers": [
                "predisposed",
                "disposed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My family takes …………………………….. over my work.",
            "description": "Precedence means importance. ",
            "answers": [
                "precendent",
                "precedent",
                "precedence"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}